# ADAM HILLS

07815 836996 adamhills91@gmail.com www.adamhills.me

		$\sim$			_
$\mathbf{r}$	へ	U	ГΙ	ш	

Web developer with over 2 years' experience in building responsive and user-friendly web pages and applications. These skills have been acquired alongside working a full-time hospitality management position, and I am now determined to join an experienced team to focus and build on my future in web development.

SKILLS —		
• HTML	• CSS	<ul> <li>JavaScript ES6</li> </ul>
• PHP	• Git	● React
EDUCATION ——		

### The Complete Web Developer: Zero to Mastery - Udemy, by Andrei Neagoie

Online course that teaches modern Web Development fundamentals and the skills required to become a full stack developer.

- HTML5, CSS and JavaScript
- Frameworks including Bootstrap and React.js
- Worked with the command line and Git/GitHub

#### freeCodeCamp

Completed the following modules:

- Responsive Web Design
- JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures
- Front End Libraries

#### Audio and Music Technology BSc

First Class Honours

- First Class grade in Web Development Module (HTML, CSS and WordPress)
- First Class grade in Programming for Audio Module (C++)

University of the West of England, Bristol 2011 - 2014

## **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

Starbucks
Store Manager
July 2018 – present

Responsible for overseeing the daily operations of the store by leading and mentoring the sales team via clear communication. We rely on excellent and long-lasting customer relationships to keep people choosing us over our competitors.

Royal Caribbean Youth Staff Feb 2016 - 2018 Responsible for delivering a range of high energy activities for children on board cruise ships, as well as hosting sports and gaming activities for the teenagers.